<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Manas Ranjan Pati</title>
    <link>https://manasranjanpati.netlify.com/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Manas Ranjan Pati</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 18 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://manasranjanpati.netlify.com/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>A poetry for Krsna</title>
      <link>https://manasranjanpati.netlify.com/posts/krishna_poetry/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://manasranjanpati.netlify.com/posts/krishna_poetry/</guid>
      <description>I bow to your Lotus Feet
Which is there in every town and street. ||
I am incomplete without your compassion
You are there behind all my satisfaction. ||
You always helped me there when I was in pain
I don&amp;rsquo;t want anything where you do not remain. ||
Hey Prabhu I want to be your eternal servant
Give me the knowledge and peace with some prevent. ||
Make me a particle in air so that I can pass by your flute as atom</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Installing Linuxbrew in Linux </title>
      <link>https://manasranjanpati.netlify.com/posts/linuxbrew/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://manasranjanpati.netlify.com/posts/linuxbrew/</guid>
      <description>Check Git Version Check your git version first by using the following command.
$ git --version git version 2.9.5 Manually install Linuxbrew to your preferred location. Switch to the directory where you want Linuxbrew installed and execute these commands
git clone https://github.com/Homebrew/brew .linuxbrew/Homebrew mkdir .linuxbrew/bin ln -s ../Homebrew/bin/brew .linuxbrew/bin eval $(.linuxbrew/bin/brew shellenv) These commands are modified from the Alternative Installation section of the Homebrew on Linux docs in order to be location-agnostic.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Django Generic Relation</title>
      <link>https://manasranjanpati.netlify.com/posts/django2/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://manasranjanpati.netlify.com/posts/django2/</guid>
      <description>Introduction
Hello and welcome. Today we will learn how to comment using django default Generic Relations or Generic Foreignkey.
In django we all know that to relate any models we can use OneToOne,ManyToOne and ForegnKey relationships. For posting comment to other model we generally used ForeignKey. But today we will learn how to make it possible.
Above is the basic things we give to a model.py file. For validation we have to use decorators and inbuilt django features.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Django Model Creation</title>
      <link>https://manasranjanpati.netlify.com/posts/django1/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://manasranjanpati.netlify.com/posts/django1/</guid>
      <description>Introduction
In this tutorial, we will create the Django models that define the fields and behaviors of the Blog application data that we will be storing. These models map the data from your Django application to the database. It’s what Django uses to generate the database tables via their object relational mapping (ORM) API called &amp;ldquo;models&amp;rdquo;.
Django models are the base thing of any django project.The main purpose of django models are to save the user data in to any database(sqlite3,MongoDB,Oracle,PostgreSQL etc)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Activities</title>
      <link>https://manasranjanpati.netlify.com/posts/django4/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://manasranjanpati.netlify.com/posts/django4/</guid>
      <description>Life is beautiful Animal Lover    View this post on Instagram         A post shared by Manas Ranjan Pati (@manasranjanpati) on Aug 23, 2018 at 5:40am PDT
   CI/CD using Docker and Gitlab    Manas&amp;rsquo;s Daily Thoughts I believe as a human entity we always wanted to be independent in every way. Above all is the financial independent.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>